Friday, exactly at 5.
Hello!
My name is Kitodar Todorov!
I am Senior Research Fellow at the I.P.C.
I.P.C. stands for the Institute For Pains In The Cock
Think about it.
How frequently do you hear from your friends, colleagues and significant others
And also from public figures
"My cock hurts." (i.e. I don't care)
"Cock pain" is a serious illness, experienced not only by men, but also women!
These experiences come from ancient times.
In Bulgaria, these become popular in the late 90s.
Today, we observe an epidemic boom of this illness.
We researched 100 patients with pains in their cocks.
Results were clear.
Cock pains depend directly on the emotional state of the patient leading to progressive dementia.
Do you think this relation between feeling pain in the cock and being stupid is accidental?
No!
"My cock hurts" symptoms vary.
Most certainly you have heard any of the following:
My dick hurts ...
My pipe hurts ...
And the German style ...
My schmeiser hurts ...
However, all patients share in common ...
They are in full denial of having any pain in the cock, regardless the showing symptoms. Thus, the diagnosing and treating this illness is really hard!
"My cock hurts"
Is this a physical or mental illness?
Is it possible to cure?
Will the National Health Fund recuperate me if I treat it?
Here's another alarming fact ...
Did you know that ...
According to the latest studies on the subject ...
Bulgaria is top leading country in the whole world ...
In having "cock pain" per capita?
What is the solution?
Our Institute developed a special treatment program
Cock pains ..
It's consisted by several phases.
The first phase takes place for around 3 weeks
During the first two weeks
The patient is prohibited from watching TV
or surfing the internet
That's done regardless of his or hers wrath ...
That's done so that he or she can build an own opinion
And ...
His personal feeling for the surrounding environment
In the end of the second week ...
He gets rid of all others' opinions
And in the end of the third week ...
The patient must express his own opinion
Which is motivated by his own will
The second part of the treatment
consists of ...
We include ...
The internet and TV
And the patient must adequately react
Without screaming
And without having a panic attack or ...
Or going crazily around the room ...
He shall express his own feelings
And his own opinion
On the question or subject he has seen on the news or
Or in a TV show
The third phase of the treatment
Is organized like a game.
We have included a variety of exercises there, like
Help other person having troubles ...
Even if you have something more important to do
Or the exercise - touch an outcast on the street
Or the exercise
Meet your family - it's your family
Here, we meet the patient with his family.
We organize a family dinner
And we see how a grown-up man in his 30s or 40s
Understands his mother for the first time
He understands his father
He understands the problems in the family
He speaks with them!
He gets to meet his brother
Or sisters, if he has such, of course
And ahm
And the last phase of the treatment is
The auto-suggestive and reassuring part where
Where the patient, before going out of bed,
has to repeat x150 times
And x150 times before going to bed
To repeat
I
do not
have any pain in my cock
We are from I.C.P. and we speak about "cock pains" ...
YOU SHOULD TOO!
Help us make Bulgaria a place
Without any pains in the cock
The truth of the matter is that my ass hurts whether someone tells me his cock hurts or not ...
Come here, I will show you
What we've made